



AlexLeybourne .com



AlexLeybourne1 @gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/ alexleybourne



github.com/ alexleybourne



Brisbane, Australia

Education

Developer Boot Camp

Coder Academy 2019 - 2020

Bachelor of Film

Griffith University 2016 - 2017

Diploma in Project Management

Frontline Management 2015

High School Diploma

Anglican Church Grammar School 2015

CERT III in Web Development

Mt.Gravatt Tafe 2014

Bronze Duke of Edinburgh 2014

Alex Leybourne Junior Developer

Profile

I am an experienced, capable and fresh-minded individual currently completing a 6 month Junior Dev Bootcamp at Coder Academy. I have previously worked in the areas of Social media, film and content creation but found myself falling in love with creating through code. I began through self-teaching using online resources. Outside of my study, I enjoy keeping up with all things tech and the rapidly expanding world it is. Playing social Basketball, taking care of my pets and travelling wherever I can.

Skills













HTML

RUBY

RAILS Javascript

Program Skills:

- Sketch
- Premiere Pro
- InVision Studio
- After Effects
- Photoshop
- Microsoft Suite

Soft Skills:

- Leaderhsip
- Growth Mindset
- Team Player
- Creative Thinking
- Problem Solving Time Management

Experience

Director of Young Minds Media

- 2016 - 2019

Branding, Graphics, Web Design and content.

Content Creator and Manager Brand Byte Digital - 2016 - 2017

Content creater for @Brisbane and Sponsor organiser.

Crew Member and Trainer

KFC - 2014 - 2017

Customer service, food preparation and leadership.

Student at Coder Academy

- 2019 - Current

Completing a 6 month fast tracked Bootcamp learning Ruby, TDD, Rails, Javascript, Mern Stack (MongoDB, Express, React, Node.js) Version control, Deployment, Debugging, project management skills and more. To Graduate as a Full Stack Developer.

Awards

GOMA - Creative Generation Award

Gallery Of Modern Art 2015

Andrew Rowan Memorial Art Prize

Anglican Church Grammar School 2015

